

Mobile No: +8801680139088

E-mail: khandokarshamstabrez@gmail.com LinkedIn: Khandokar Shams Tabrez Raiyan

CAREER GOAL

Would like to build my career in an organization's Human Resource Department where I will get to learn new things and where international standards are strictly followed. Instead of running behind money, I would like to gather experiences like no other and excel in the path I follow to fulfil my dreams.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1. Organization: Samsung R&D Institute Bangladesh Ltd.

Department: Human Resources.

Designation: Intern, Talent Acquisition (November 2019 – March 2020)

Duties/Responsibilities:

• CV sorting and CV bank management.

- Assisting in pre-employment examination.
- Arranging and coordinating interview sessions.
- Assisting in interview calls and job candidate handling.
- Keeping employees files and records in chronological manner.
- Coordinating and assisting in day-to-day training operational activities.
- Maintaining the employee's personal file with all related papers as updated.
- Assisting in pre-employment HR activities and induction session (Documentation and Filing).

2. Organization: Expo Group, Bangladesh.

Department: Human Resources.

Designation: HRIS Data Operator (August 2019 – October 2019)

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Entering Employee data from source documents within time limits.
- Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting information to prepare source data for computer entry.
- Reviewing data for deficiencies or errors, correcting any incompatibilities and checking output.
- Correcting errors and organizing the information in a manner that will optimize swift and accurate capturing.
- **3. Organization:** The Westin Dhaka.

Designation: Management Trainee Officer (February 2017 – May 2017)

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Making Pro Forma for the coming events.
- Responsible for the day-to-day sales and marketing work.
- Talking to foreign guests, taking their grievance and trying to solve them.
- Making sales call and sales offers to different Multinational and National companies.

4. Organization: Radisson Blu Dhaka Water Garden.

Department: Food & Beverage Service.

Designation: Trainee (March 2016 – May 2016)



EDUCATION

1. PGDHRM (Enrolled) United International University (UIU)

Post Graduate Diploma in Human Resources

Management.

2. MBA (2019) Independent University, Bangladesh (IUB)

Master of Business Administration.

Major: Human Resources Management.

CGPA: 3.08

3. BTHM (2016) Victoria University of Bangladesh (VUB)

Bachelor of Tourism & Hospitality Management.

CGPA: 3.78

4. ISC (2011) Himalayan International Residential School (HIRS)

Indian School Certificate.

New Delhi Board. Commercial Studies. Percentage: 70%

TRAINING

1. Training Title: Computer Office Application

Institute: Bangladesh Technical Education Board (BTEB)

Year: 2019

2. Training Title: Data Handling Procedures

Institute: The Westin Dhaka

Year: 2017

3. Training Title: Marriott + Starwood Overview

Institute: The Westin Dhaka

Year: 2017

SKILLS

- Good computer knowledge in M.S Word, M.S Excel, M.S Power Point & M.S Access.
- Excellent commend over the **English** language both spoken and written.
- Believes in **Team Work**.
- Yes, I Can attitude.

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Took part in the Dhaka International 10 Km. Marathon Run 2013, completed successfully, and was awarded with a participation medal.
- Was appointed as the Head Boy of the school and college for the academic year 2009-2011.
- Was awarded as the Spirit of HIRS (the highest award given to an individual student in the school) in the year 2011.
- Was awarded thrice with the All Round Contribution and Outstanding Achievement Award for the academic year 2007-2008, 2008-2009 and 2010-2011.
- Was awarded with the Outstanding Achievement Award in Community Service in the year 2011.
- Took part in Bangla Debate from the academic year 2005-2011 and was awarded winner and runners up respectively.
- Represented HIRS in different interschool Dance Competition and Football Competitions from 2007-2011 and was awarded with Participation Certificates Respectively.
- Respectively achieved many awards in the field of athletics, which consists of track events (100m, 200m, 400m and 800m) Shot Put, Javelin and Discus.
- Respectively achieved many awards in the field of swimming which consists of three strokes (Front Crawl, Back Stroke and Breast Stroke).

PERSONAL INFORMATION

• Father's Name : Late. Khandoker Ali Ahad.

Mother's Name : Rahmina Beauty.
Spouse's Name : Tahmina Islam.
Date & Place of Birth : 09 May 1991 Dhaka.

Sex : Male.
Religion : Islam.
Nationality : Bangladeshi.
National ID No. : 595 414 2054

• **Birth Certificate No** : 19912692511154766

Passport No. : BE 0978783Marital Status : Married.

Present Address
 House No 11, Road No 12, Kallyanpur, Dhaka-1207.
 Permanent Address
 Bhogdaburi, Chilahati, P.O. Domar, Dist. Nilphamari.

REFERENCE

Gazi Munir Uddin

Sr. Professional and Head of HR Samsung R&D Institute Bangladesh Ltd.

Email: munir.hr@samsung.com Contact No: +8801730783287 Relationship: Professional.

Md. Bashiur Rahman Abir

Executive - Talent Acquisition **Human Resources** Expo Holdings (BD) Ltd.

Email: abir@expogroup-bd.com Contact No: +8801847052223 Relationship: Professional.

DECLARATION

I do here by declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge.

SIGNATURE

(Khandokar Shams Tabrez Raiyan)